<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>CSH</type>
		<description>CSH labels for FlexForm fields</description>
		<csh_table>tx_adgooglemaps_pi1</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:ad_google_maps/Resources/Private/Language/locallang_tca_csh_map.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array"></labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">The map title.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Check this box if you wish to hide the content element from being displayed.</label>
			<label index="categories.description">Record storge for categories to display on the map.</label>

			<label index="map_type_id.description">The initial Map mapTypeId. Required.</label>
			<label index="width.description">The initial width of the map.</label>
			<label index="height.description">The initial height of the map.</label>
			<label index="background_color.description">Color used for the background of the Map div. This color will be visible when tiles have not yet loaded as the user pans. This option can only be set when the map is initialized.</label>
			<label index="min_zoom.description">The minimum zoom level which will be displayed on the map. If omitted, or set to null, the minimum zoom from the current map type is used instead.</label>
			<label index="max_zoom.description">The maximum zoom level which will be displayed on the map. If omitted, or set to null, the maximum zoom from the current map type is used instead.</label>
			<label index="no_clear.description">If true, do not clear the contents of the Map div.</label>
			<label index="center_type.description">The initial map center.</label>
			<label index="center.description">Coordinate of the map center.</label>
			<label index="zoom.description">The initial Map zoom level. Required.</label>
			<label index="use_marker_cluster.description">This option creates and manages per-zoom-level clusters for large amounts of markers.</label>

			<label index="disable_default_ui.description">Enables/disables all default UI. May be overridden individually.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control.description">The initial enabled/disabled state of the Map type control.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_map_type_ids.description">IDs of map types to show in the control.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_RIGHT.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_style.description">Style id. Used to select what style of map type control to display.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control.description">The initial enabled/disabled state of the navigation control.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control_options_style.description">Style id. Used to select what style of navigation control to display.</label>
			<label index="scale_control.description">The initial enabled/disabled state of the scale control.</label>
			<label index="scale_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is BOTTOM_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="pan_control.description">The enabled/disabled state of the pan control.</label>
			<label index="pan_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control.description">The enabled/disabled state of the zoom control.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control_options_style.description">Style id. Used to select what style of zoom control to display.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control.description">The initial enabled/disabled state of the Street View pegman control. The Street View pegman control is enabled by default.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. Klick for details.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control_options_position.details">The default position is embedded within the navigation control. If this position is empty or the same as that specified in the navigationControlOptions, the Street View control will be displayed as part of the navigation control. Otherwise, it will be displayed separately.</label>
			<label index="search_control.description">Activates the simple map search.</label>
			<label index="search_marker.description">If user search is used you can define an own marker here. At default the search marker of the MapDrawer is used.</label>

			<label index="disable_double_click_zoom.description">Enables/disables zoom and center on double click. Enabled by default.</label>
			<label index="scrollwheel.description">If false, disables scrollwheel zooming on the map. The scrollwheel is enabled by default.</label>
			<label index="draggable.description">If false, prevents the map from being dragged. Dragging is enabled by default.</label>
			<label index="draggable_cursor.description">The name or url of the cursor to display on a draggable object.</label>
			<label index="dragging_cursor.description">The name or url of the cursor to display when an object is dragging.</label>
			<label index="keyboard_shortcuts.description">If false, prevents the map from being controled by the keyboard. Keyboard shortcuts are enabled by default.</label>

			<label index="info_window_keep_open.description">If set, info windows keep open if an other get open.</label>
			<label index="info_window_behaviour.description">Set the behaviour for all info windows.</label>
			<label index="info_window_object_number.description">This option is a optionSplit configuaration. This settings have only effects on layers with the type marker or if "Add marker" is set. To parse more then one object in an info window seperate objects with an comma.</label>
			<label index="info_window_close_on_click.description">If set info window will be closed by clicking the object again.</label>
			<label index="info_window_close_all_on_map_click.description">If set all info windows will be closed if map is clicked.</label>
			<label index="info_window_disable_auto_pan.description">Disable auto-pan on open. By default, the info window will pan the map so that it is fully visible when it opens.</label>
			<label index="info_window_max_width.description">Maximum width of the infowindow, regardless of content's width. This value is only considered if it is set before a call to open. To change the maximum width when changing content, call close, setOptions, and then open.</label>
			<label index="info_window_pixel_offset_width.description">The offset, in pixels, of the tip of the info window from the point on the map at whose geographical coordinates the info window is anchored. If an InfoWindow is opened with an anchor, the pixelOffset will be calculated from the top-center of the anchor's bounds.</label>
			<label index="info_window_pixel_offset_height.description">The offset, in pixels, of the tip of the info window from the point on the map at whose geographical coordinates the info window is anchored. If an InfoWindow is opened with an anchor, the pixelOffset will be calculated from the top-center of the anchor's bounds.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Titel der Karte.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Ist diese Option aktiviert, wird das Element nicht auf der Seite angezeigt.</label>
			<label index="categories.description">Datensatzsammlung für Kategorien die auf der Karte angezeigt werden.</label>

			<label index="map_type_id.description">Anfängliche mapTypeId der Karte. Erforderlich.</label>
			<label index="width.description">Anfängliche Breite der Karte.</label>
			<label index="height.description">Anfängliche Höhe der Karte.</label>
			<label index="background_color.description">Für den Hintergrund der Karten-div verwendete Farbe. Diese Farbe wird angezeigt, wenn noch keine Kacheln geladen wurden und der Nutzer die Karte schwenkt. Diese Option kann nur festgelegt werden, wenn die Karte initiiert ist.</label>
			<label index="min_zoom.description">Die min. Zoomstufe welche auf der Karte dargestellt werden soll. Wenn der Wert nicht gesetzt ist, wird die min. Zoomstufe des aktuellen Kartentyps verwendet.</label>
			<label index="max_zoom.description">Die max. Zoomstufe welche auf der Karte dargestellt werden soll. Wenn der Wert nicht gesetzt ist, wird die max. Zoomstufe des aktuellen Kartentyps verwendet.</label>
			<label index="no_clear.description">Falls wahr, den Inhalt der Karten-div nicht löschen.</label>
			<label index="center_type.description">Anfängliches Kartenzentrum. Erforderlich.</label>
			<label index="center.description">Koordinaten des Kartenzentrum.</label>
			<label index="zoom.description">Anfängliche Zoomstufe der Karte. Erforderlich.</label>
			<label index="use_marker_cluster.description">Diese Option erstellt und managed die Pro-Zoom-Level-Cluster für eine große Anzahl an Markierungen.</label>

			<label index="disable_default_ui.description">Aktiviert/inaktiviert alle Standard-UI. Kann im Einzelfall außer Kraft gesetzt werden.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control.description">Anfänglicher Aktivierungs-/Inaktivierungsstatus der Kartentypsteuerung.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_map_type_ids.description">IDs von Kartentypen, die im Steuerelement angezeigt werden sollen.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_position.description">Positions-ID. Hiermit wird die Position des Steuerelements auf der Karte festgelegt. Die Standardposition ist TOP_RIGHT.</label>
			<label index="map_type_control_options_style.description">Stil-ID. Wird verwendet, um auszuwählen, welcher Stil der Kartentypsteuerung angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control.description">Anfänglicher Aktivierungs-/Inaktivierungsstatus der Navigationssteuerung.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control_options_position.description">Positions-ID. Hiermit wird die Position des Steuerelements auf der Karte festgelegt. Die Standardposition ist TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="navigation_control_options_style.description">Stil-ID. Wird verwendet, um auszuwählen, welcher Stil der Navigationstypsteuerung angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="scale_control.description">Anfänglicher Aktivierungs-/Inaktivierungsstatus der Maßstabssteuerung.</label>
			<label index="scale_control_options_position.description">Positions-ID. Hiermit wird die Position des Steuerelements auf der Karte festgelegt. Die Standardposition ist BOTTOM_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="scale_control_options_style.description">Stil-ID. Wird verwendet, um auszuwählen, welcher Stil der Maßstabssteuerung angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="pan_control.description">The enabled/disabled state of the pan control.</label>
			<label index="pan_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control.description">The enabled/disabled state of the zoom control.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</label>
			<label index="zoom_control_options_style.description">Style id. Used to select what style of zoom control to display.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control.description">Der anfängliche Status (aktiviert/deaktiviert) des Street View-Männchen-Steuerelements.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control_options_position.description">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. Klick for details.</label>
			<label index="street_view_control_options_position.details">The default position is embedded within the navigation control. If this position is empty or the same as that specified in the navigationControlOptions, the Street View control will be displayed as part of the navigation control. Otherwise, it will be displayed separately.</label>
			<label index="search_control.description">Aktivier die einfache Kartensuche.</label>
			<label index="search_marker.description">Wenn die Benutzersuche verwendet wird, kann hier eine eigene Markierung definieren werden. Standardmäßig wird die Markierung des MapDrawer verwendet.</label>

			<label index="disable_double_click_zoom.description">Aktiviert/deaktiviert das Zoomen und Zentrieren durch Doppelklick. Standardmäßig aktiviert.</label>
			<label index="scrollwheel.description">Falls falsch, ist das Zoomen der Karte mit dem Scrollrad inaktiviert. Das Scrollrad ist standardmäßig aktiviert.</label>
			<label index="draggable.description">Falls falsch, kann die Karte nicht verschoben werden. Verschieben ist standardmäßig aktiviert.</label>
			<label index="draggable_cursor.description">Der Name oder der URL des Cursors, der für ein verschiebbares Objekt angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="dragging_cursor.description">Der Name oder der URL des Cursors, der angezeigt werden soll, wenn ein Objekt verschoben wird.</label>
			<label index="keyboard_shortcuts.description">Falls falsch, kann die Karte nicht über die Tastatur gesteuert werden. Tastaturkürzel sind standardmäßig aktiviert.</label>

			<label index="info_window_keep_open.description">Wenn gesetzt, bleiben Infofenster offen sobald man ein anderes öffnet.</label>
			<label index="info_window_behaviour.description">Setzt das Verhalten für alle Infofenster.</label>
			<label index="info_window_object_number.description">Diese Option ist eine optionSplit-Konfiguration. Diese Einstellung betrifft nur Ebenen mit dem Typ Markierung oder wenn "Markierung hinzufügen" gesetzt ist. Um mehrere Seiteninhalte in einem Infofenster darzustellen, trenne die Objekte mit einem Komma.</label>
			<label index="info_window_close_on_click.description">Wenn gesetzt wird das Infofenster geschlossen sobald man erneut auf das Objekt klickt.</label>
			<label index="info_window_close_all_on_map_click.description">Wenn gesetzt werden alle Infofenster geschlossen sobald man auf die Karte klickt.</label>
			<label index="info_window_disable_auto_pan.description">Deaktiviere Auto-Schwenk beim Öffnen. Standardmäßig wird ein Infofenster auf der Karte so verschoben, sodass es geöffnet voll sichtbar ist.</label>
			<label index="info_window_max_width.description">Die maximale Breite des Infofensters, ungeachtet der Breite des Inhalts. Dieser Wert wird nur dann berücksichtigt, wenn er vor dem Aufrufen von Öffnen festgelegt wurde. Um die maximale Breite gleichzeitig mit dem Inhalt zu ändern, rufen Sie close, dann setOptions und dann open auf.</label>
			<label index="info_window_pixel_offset_width.description">Der Abstand in Pixeln zwischen der Spitze des Infofensters und dem Punkt auf der Karte, an dessen geografischen Koordinaten das Infofenster verankert ist. Wenn ein InfoWindow mit einem Anker geöffnet wird, wird pixelOffset anhand des oberen Zentrums der Ankergrenzen berechnet.</label>
			<label index="info_window_pixel_offset_height.description">Der Abstand in Pixeln zwischen der Spitze des Infofensters und dem Punkt auf der Karte, an dessen geografischen Koordinaten das Infofenster verankert ist. Wenn ein InfoWindow mit einem Anker geöffnet wird, wird pixelOffset anhand des oberen Zentrums der Ankergrenzen berechnet.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>